I want you to hit me as hard as you can
why how much can you know about yourself
you never been in fight wait let me
start earlier like many of you I was
stuck
you want me to deprioritize my current
reports yet until you advise them status
upgrade make these your primary action
items I couldn't sleep
no you can't die from insomnia I'd flip
through catalogs and wonder what kind of
dining set defines me as a person this
is your life and it's ending one minute
at a time I prayed for a different life
so I make in the same suit this is how I
met Tyler Durden come on hit before I
lose my nerve it was on the tip of
everyone's tongue can I be next we just
gave it a name gentlemen welcome to
Fight Club
first rule of Fight Club is Wow nice you
do not talk about Fight Club I think
your blood some of it yeah
after Fight Club we all started seeing
things differently here you don't have
to keep me up
and she ruined everything you're not
into her no God not at all well been
raised on television to believe that one
day we'd all be millionaires and movie
gods and rock stars but we won't they
had a plan to what purpose
in Tyler we trusted I got a fight club
up and on each one of you has a homework
assignment you're gonna start a fight
with a total stranger you were looking
for a way to change your life you got it
I'm stopping this
[Music]
Wow anyone who would you fight Shatner I
play William Shatner
[Music]